Okay, Chandler, Mon, there's only one banana nut muffin left.
好啦，錢德勒、摩妮卡，只剩下一個香蕉核桃馬芬了。
Well, order mine first.
那就先點我的。
Yeah, but I'm so much faster.
是啊，但我動作快得多。
Give it to me.
給我。
No.
不。
Give it to me.
給我吧。
Okay, you can have it.
好吧，給你。
There you go. Enjoy your coffee.
這個給你。好好享用你的咖啡。
That was there when I got here.
我剛來的時候那就在這了。
Hey, you guys, you will never guess who's coming to New York.
嘿，各位，你們絕對猜不到誰要來紐約了。
Wait, Phoebe, tell us before you can swallow.
等等，菲比，嚥下東西前先告訴我們。
Okay, Ryan, that guy I went out with who's in the Navy.
好吧，是瑞恩，那個和我約會過、在海軍服役的傢伙。
You went out with a guy in the Navy?
你跟海軍約會過？
Yeah, I met him when I was playing guitar in Washington Square Park.
對啊，我在華盛頓廣場公園彈吉他時認識他的。
Ryan threw in saltwater taffy because he didn't have any change.
瑞恩丟了鹹水太妃糖給我，因為他沒零錢。
Hey, is that when you rode saltwater taffy, man?
嘿，老兄，那就是你創作「鹹水太妃糖」這首歌的時候嗎？
No.
不是。
No, he is my submarine guy.
不，他是我的潛水艇男孩。
He resurfaces, like, every couple years,
他大概每幾年才會浮出水面一次，
and we have the most amazing three days together.
然後我們會一起度過最不可思議的三天。
Only this time, he's coming for two weeks.
不過這次，他會待上整整兩個星期。
Two whole weeks, which means, yay!
整整兩個星期，意思是說，耶！
So, wait, this guy goes down for, like, two years at a time?
所以，等等，這傢伙一次潛下去就是在下面待個兩年？
Mm-mm.
嗯哼。
That'll teach you to lick my muffin.
這就是你舔我馬芬的下場。
Hi.
嗨。
Oh, no, what happened?
噢不能，發生什麼事了？
I just spoke to Carol. Ben's got the chicken pox.
我剛跟卡蘿通完電話。班得了水痘。
Oh, are you kidding?
噢，你開玩笑吧？
Yeah, so if you haven't already had it, chances are you're gonna get it.
對，所以如果你們還沒得過，很有可能會被傳染。
Well, I've had it.
嗯，我得過了。
Yeah, I've had it.
對，我得過了。
Had it.
得過了。
Well, I haven't ever had it. I feel so left out.
嗯，我從來沒得過。覺得自己好被排擠喔。
Oh, look!
哦，看！
So no one told you life was gonna be this way
所以沒人告訴過你生活會是這樣
Your job's a joke, you're broke
工作是個笑話，你身無分文
Your love life's the only way
你的感情生活就是這樣
It's like you're always stuck in second gear
就像你總是被卡在二檔
When it hasn't been your day, week, or month
當這不是屬於你的一天、一週或一個月
Or even your year
甚至不是屬於你的一年
But I'll be there for you
但我會在你身邊
When the rain starts to pour
當大雨傾盆時
I'll be there for you
我會在你身邊
I'll be there for you too
我也會在你身邊
Honey, you made the bed again.
親愛的，你又重新鋪了一次床。
I told you, you don't have to do that.
我跟你說過你不用這樣做。
This isn't camp.
這裡又不是夏令營。
Oh, then I guess the panty raid last night was totally uncalled for.
噢，那我猜昨晚去女生宿舍偷內褲的行動完全是多此一舉了囉。
Okay, I am going to take a shower,
好了，我要去洗澡了，
and today I will be singing Jim Croce's Leroy Brown.
而且今天我要高唱 Jim Croce 的 Leroy Brown。
Monica!
摩妮卡！
Hey, Mon.
嘿，小摩。
I have a question.
我有一個問題。
Is Leroy the baddest man in the whole damn town
Leroy 是全鎮「最壞的男人」
or the fattest man in the whole damn town?
還是全鎮「最胖的男人」？
The baddest.
最壞的男人。
Otherwise, the song would be Fat, Fat Leroy Brown.
不然這首歌就會變成胖子、胖子 Leroy Brown 了。
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
I'm just waiting for you, sweetie.
我只是在等你啊，親愛的。
Are you remaking the bed?
你在重新鋪床嗎？
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
對不起。對不起。
You know what? The way you did it, it was just fine.
你知道嗎？你剛剛鋪的樣子其實很不錯。
Then you're redoing it because?
那你還要重鋪是因為？
If I tell you, you'll think I'm crazy.
如果我告訴你，你會覺得我瘋了。
You're pretty much running that risk either way.
不管怎樣你都已經冒著讓我這麼覺得的風險了。
Okay, you see,
好，你看，
the duvet tag shouldn't be at the top left corner.
羽絨被的標籤不該在左上角。
It should be at the bottom right corner.
它應該在右下角。
Oh, well, that's not so crazy.
噢，那也沒那麼瘋狂拉。
I'm just easing you in.
我這只是個開場白。
All right.
好吧。
All right, you see these little flower blossoms?
好，你看到這些小花苞嗎？
They should be facing up, not down,
它們的頭應該要朝上，不是朝下，
because, well, the head of the bed is where the sun would be.
因為床頭就是太陽的方向。
You don't love me anymore.
你不再愛我了。
Actually, if it's possible, I love you more.
事實上，如果可以的話，我反而更愛你。
Really?
真的嗎？
Wow. Well, then, come on.
哇喔。那麼，過來吧。
I want to show you how to fold a toilet paper into a point.
我想給你看看怎麼把衛生紙摺成一個尖角。
Hey, look, Joey, I'm just saying,
嘿，聽著，喬伊，我只是覺得，
if you need something to hold you over,
如果你需要一份可以撐一下的工作，
I can get you a job right here as an entry-level processor.
我可以幫你在這裡找一份初級資料處理員的職缺。
But don't you need experience for a job like that?
但做這個不用經驗嗎？
It's not that hard to learn.
這沒那麼難學。
And as for people realizing that you have no idea what you're doing,
至於要是大家發現你根本不知道自己在幹嘛這點嘛，
hey, you're an actor. Act like a processor.
嘿，你可是演員。就演成一個資料處理員啊。
People will think you're a processor.
那大家就會以為你是一個真正的資料處理員了。
Hey, Chandler, here's this morning's projection.
嘿，錢德勒，這是今天早上的預測報表。
Hey, thanks. Scott Alexander, Joey Tribbiani.
嘿，謝啦。史考特·亞歷山大，這位是喬伊·崔比雅尼。
Hey.
嘿。
Joey is a, uh, fellow processor.
喬伊他，呃，也是我們資料處理的同事。
No kidding.
不開玩笑吧。
Oh, yeah, yeah.
噢對，沒錯。
I process. People want the processing.
我是處理員。大家想要處理資料。
I'm the one they call.
他們就會找我。
Where do you work?
你在哪高就？
Uh, well, right now I'm in between things.
嗯，我現在是在空窗期啦。
You know how it is. One day you're processing,
你知道這行嘛，可能今天還有料要處理，
the next day you're not so much processing anymore.
明天就沒什麼好處理了。
I was just telling Joey about the opening in Fleischman's Group.
我剛剛正告訴喬伊關於弗雷希曼小組的職缺。
Fleischman's Group?
弗雷希曼小組？
Whatever you do, don't touch his sandwiches.
不管你遇到誰，千萬不要碰他的三明治。
Are all you processors dorks?
你們做資料處理的都這麼怪胎阿？
Ugh. This lipstick looks just great on you.
呃，這支口紅塗在你嘴上真好看。
You look fabulous, honey. You really do.
你美極了，親愛的，真的。
Yeah? Are you sure? Really?
是嗎？確定？真的？
See? You look beautiful. For God's sakes, dim the lights.
看？你很美啊。看在老天的份上，把燈調暗點。
Are you... I...
你是...我...
I'm hideous.
我醜死了。
It's gonna be okay.
一切都會沒事的。
Ryan's been underwater.
瑞恩都在海裡面待那麼久了。
He's just gonna be so glad that you don't have barbs anymore.
光想到你身上沒有長滿海藻，他就該偷笑了。
Come in.
請進。
Hey, baby, I'm back.
嘿，寶貝，我回來了。
Hey, Ryan, what's up?
嘿，瑞恩，怎麼啦？
What's going on?
怎麼了？
Oh, no, no. You know, you have to stay back.
噢，不...不行。你得離我遠點。
I... I have the pox.
我...我長水痘了。
Hey.
嘿。
Chicken or small?
水痘 (chicken pox) 還是天花 (smallpox)？
Chicken, which is so ironic,
是水痘 (chicken)，滿諷刺的，
considering I'm a vegetarian.
畢竟我是個吃純素的人。
Why aren't you at home in bed?
你為什麼不躺在家的床上？
Because my grandmother's never had chicken pox.
因為我外婆從沒得過水痘。
Please, please tell me you have,
拜託，求你告訴我你得過了，
because, oh, my God, I forgot how cute you are.
因為，我的老天，我都忘了你有多可愛了。
I'm sorry. I never had them.
抱歉，我從沒得過。
If I had one wish,
如果我可以許一個願，
it would be to build a time machine, go back to when I was seven.
那就是建造一台時光機，回到七歲的時候。
When Jimmy Houser had the chicken pox,
當吉米·豪瑟得水痘的時後，
I would grab that kid and rub him all over my face.
我一定要抓住那孩子，把他的臉到處亂揉。
Yeah, or, you know,
是啊，或著，你知道的，
you could just wish that I didn't have them now.
你也可以祈禱我現在身上沒長這些。
Can I please see your face?
我能看看你的臉嗎？
No.
不行。
You don't want to see your face covered with pox.
你不會想看到一張長滿水痘的臉的。
Your face could be covered with locks. I wouldn't care.
哪怕你的臉上都是密碼鎖，我也不在乎。
And you hate fish.
而你討厭魚(或者海草)。
Oh.
噢。
So sweet.
好甜。
All right. Okay.
好吧，歐給。
All right, you can see.
好啦，你看吧。
This is me.
這就是我。
Oh, sorry.
噢抱歉。
Oh, I am scary.
噢，這真的很可怕。
Sorry, the lightning.
抱歉，這是閃電 (被閃電嚇到)。
Lightning was an unfortunate coincidence.
剛好有閃電真是個不幸的巧合。
You look lovely.
你看起來很美麗。
Lovely.
美麗極了。
I hate this.
我討厭這樣。
Can I tell you, I had the most amazing two weeks planned for us,
這我一定要跟你說，我本來為我們計畫了最棒的兩週，
and almost everything I had in mind,
而在我想像中的每一件事裡，
we had to be a lot closer than this.
我們的距離都得比現在這樣近得多。
Phoebe, I have spent the last eight months
菲比，過去這八個月裡，
in a steel tube with men.
我都和一群男人擠在鐵管裡面。
Thinking about this moment,
想著這一刻的回來到來，
I am not going to let a bunch of
我絕對不會讓這些
itchy spots
發癢的小疹子
stand between us.
阻礙我們。
Okay, this is the most romantic disease I've ever had.
好吧，這可真是我得過最浪漫的病了。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, how's the first week going?
嘿，第一週過得怎麼樣啊？
Pretty good. It's like you said.
很順利。就如你所說，
It's mostly just putting numbers from one column
就只是把其中一欄的數字
into another column.
搬到另一欄去而已。
Well, there you go.
嗯，那不就結了。
Hey, and everybody is so nice.
嘿，而且大家都超好的。
I just had a good talk with that lady with the red hair, Jeannie.
我剛才還和那個紅頭髮女士 Jeannie 相處得滿愉快的。
Jeannie? The head of East Coast Operations, Jeannie?
Jeannie？東岸營運主管 Jeannie？
Yeah.
對阿。
Turns out our kids go to the same school.
我們剛好聊到我們的小孩上同一間學校。
Yeah.
阿哈。
Small world, huh?
世界真小，對吧？
Weird world.
這世界真怪。
Your kids?
你的小孩？
I figure my character has kids.
我覺得我這個角色應該要有小孩才合理。
You know, there isn't a part of that sentence
你知道，其實剛才你說的那句話裡，沒有一個部分，
that I don't need explained?
是不需要解釋給我聽的。
Well, see, when you're acting,
嗯，你看，演戲的時候嘛，
you need to think about stuff like that.
你就是得設定好這些細節。
My character, Joseph the Processing Guy,
我演的角色，Joseph，身為一個資料處理員，
has two little girls,
有兩個小女兒，
Ashley and Brittany.
Ashley 和 Brittany。
Ashley copies everything Brittany does.
Ashley 做什麼事都學 Brittany。
Oh.
噢。
Well, invisible kids can be that way sometimes.
嗯，有時候看不見的小孩就是這樣。
You know, Joseph and his wife, Karen,
你知道嗎，Joseph 和他太太 Karen，
are thinking of having a third kid.
正在考慮要生第三個小孩。
You know what?
你猜怎麼著？
Just did.
有了。
Really? Wow.
真的？哇喔。
That's some pretty powerful imaginary sperm you must have there.
看來你的幻想精子滿有威力的嘛。
You know what makes the itching even worse?
你知道有什麼東西會讓你更癢嗎？
That you don't stop talking about it?
你這張停不下來抱怨的嘴嗎？
Fine.
好吧。
Let's just play, okay?
我們繼續玩吧，好嗎？
Good. Okay.
很好。
Here we go. Double sixes.
來了。兩個六。
Here we go.
換我。
換我了。
Come to mama.
骰子乖，過來媽媽這。
Getting ready to roll the dice.
準備扔骰子了。
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Are you scratching?
你在抓癢對吧？
No. This is what I do for luck, okay?
才沒有。這不過是能幫我祈求好運的動作罷了，好嗎？
You're scratching.
你真的在抓！
Give me the dice. No.
骰子給我。不給。
Give me the dice.
給我。
Here, there. Double sixes.
來了。兩個六。
We can't scratch. You know we can't.
我們不能抓的。你知道的。
We'll scar.
我們身上會留疤的。
I can't stop thinking about it.
我滿腦子都是很想抓的念頭。
It's so hard.
這真的太難了。
I just want to grab all these houses and rub them all over my body.
我只想拿起這些（大富翁的）小房子，把它們全搓在我身上。
No.
不行。
Come on.
求你啦。
You know you want it.
我知道你也想抓的。
You know you want it too. Come on.
你也一定很想阿，來嘛。
Let's just be bad. It'll feel so good.
我們就做壞事吧。肯定超舒服。
Come on.
別忍了。
Uh-huh.
嗯。
God help me.
上帝幫幫我。
Yeah.
呼。
Okay, good. Now do me.
好，很好。現在換幫我弄。
Do my back. Come on. Harder.
幫我抓背。快點。再大力點。
There you go. Don't move.
很好喔。別停！
Why?
為什麼？
Oh.
噢。
Okay.
好。
Stop that.
停下來。
Stop that right now.
快點停下來。
You know, I might have expected this of you, Phoebe,
菲比，我可能早就料到你會有這反應，
but Ryan, you're a military man.
但瑞恩，你可是一名軍人。
She made me do it.
是她逼我的。
Oh, that's a nice color on you.
哦，那顏色真配你。
Yeah, well, it comes in pink and blotchy, baby.
這就是粉紅又起疹的顏色，寶貝。
I hope you get a weenie pock.
我希望你的GG上也長一顆水痘。
You and Milton have to join us on the boat.
你和彌爾頓這次必須和我們一起搭船去。
Karen will pack a lunch.
凱倫可以帶你們去吃午餐。
You'll bring the kids. We'll make a day of it.
你們帶著你們的小孩，我們會度過充實的一天。
Oh, that sounds lovely.
聽起來真棒。
We're going to have to set that up.
我們一定要約個時間。
Oh, I better get back.
噢，我該回去了。
Hope the baby feels better.
希望小寶寶能好點。
Oh, thanks. Thanks.
噢，謝謝。謝謝啦。
Bye-bye, Jeannie.
拜拜。珍妮。
What a phony.
真是什麼騙子都有。
Well, I'm sure you'll teach her a lesson
好吧，我相信總有一天你會讓她記取教訓的，
when she steps off the dock onto nothing.
比如當她從港口走下來什麼都沒有發現的時候。
Hey, Mr. Douglas. Sir?
嘿，道格拉斯先生，對嗎？
Uh, listen, Bing, I received your memo,
呃，聽著，賓先生，我收到你的備忘錄了，
so we're not going to see the systems report until next Friday?
所以我們要到下週五才會看到系統報告是嗎？
Well, the people in my group want to spend
因為我們這一組的人想利用這個連續假日，
the holiday weekend with their family.
多一點時間陪家人。
I have a family. I'm going to be here.
我也有家人啊，但我還是會在這邊。
Yeah, Bing.
是吧，賓先生。
What's that about?
那是怎麼一回事？
I want to give people a little slack,
我想讓大家放鬆一點，
you know, for morale.
你知道，這樣對士氣有幫助。
Look, if you want to see some rough numbers,
聽好，如果您只是想看一些大概數字的話，
I can get them to you by Wednesday.
我禮拜三前可以給你。
Rough numbers?
大概數字？
This company was not built on rough numbers.
這家公司可不是建立在「大概的數字」上的。
Am I right, Mr. Douglas?
我說得對吧，道格拉斯先生？
Have the final numbers on my desk by Tuesday.
請在星期二的時候，把最後的數字放在我桌上。
If you say so, sir.
如果您堅持的話，長官。
Joseph's good, isn't he?
這個約瑟夫表現不錯，對吧？
Well, I'm going to kill you.
是阿，我絕對要宰了你。
Hey, hey.
嘿，聽著。
I just figured Joseph's the kind of guy
我想這個約瑟夫應該也是個這方面的人才，
who likes to mix it up.
很喜歡攪和這些事。
You know, get in there, ruffle some feathers.
你懂得，深入敵營，故意去惹毛誰的。
Why?
為什麼他要這樣？
Look, I'm sorry,
這點我真的很抱歉，
but that's what Joseph does.
不過這就是約瑟夫會做的事。
Okay?
了解嗎？
If you try to pull something,
若是你想搞些什麼小花招，
he'll call you on it.
他一定會直接點出來。
What are you trying to pull, he'll say.
像是「你想耍什麼花招」，他就會這樣問。
Ooh, duct tape.
喔，是防水布膠帶。
Was I supposed to bring something, too?
所以我也還需要繼續拿別的東西來嗎？
This is for the scratchy twins out there.
我是要給外面那些快被抓癢逼瘋的雙胞胎用的。
I taped oven mitts to their hands.
我用膠帶把烤箱手套黏在他們手上。
You're strict.
你真嚴格。
Yeah, well, it's for their own good.
這可是為了他們好。
You know, I like
你懂我為甚麼喜歡
the way you have efficiently
你這麼俐落乾脆地
folded this tab under.
就把這些膠帶捲到底下的樣子嗎。
See, in a tape emergency,
你看，要是在這個有關膠帶的緊急狀況時，
you could shave valuable seconds off your time.
你就可以幫我們爭取幾秒鐘寶貴的時間了。
Exactly.
一點也沒錯。
Oh.
噢。
I love that I can be totally neurotic
我真的很喜歡、在現在這情況中
around you now.
完完全全為了你瘋狂。
Tell me the truth.
老實跟我說吧。
Don't you like it better now that everything on your desk
你現在難道沒有比以前那桌上
is perpendicular?
東西全擺在一起的情況喜歡這一切嗎？
If it's not a right angle, it is a wrong angle.
如果它看起來是不對（right）的角度，那它就是一個錯的（wrong）角度。
Very good.
講的不錯喔。
Thank you.
感謝。
You know what? Tomorrow, I'm going to do your clocks.
你猜怎麼著？明天，我要把你的那些老鐘給辦了。
You're going to do what to my clocks?
你到底要對我的那些鐘做了什麼？
I'm going to set them to my time.
我要把它們調成跟我一樣的時區。
Well, I'm confused.
這可真把我搞糊塗了。
I thought we shared time.
我以為我們是活在同一的時間點。
No, no.
沒有、才沒呢。
See, in my bedroom,
你懂嗎？在我的房間裡，
I set my clocks six minutes fast.
我把時鐘調快了六分鐘。
You want to know why?
我想知道為什麼嗎？
Because it's in a slightly different time zone than the kitchen?
因為它剛好在這邊這個有那麼一點的時差的廚房裡？
You know what? Forget it.
你才怎麼著？算了。
I'm not going to tell you.
我才不想跟你說呢。
No, come on. Come on. Tell me.
別這樣嘛。別這樣啊，告訴我好不好？
No, because you don't understand.
不要，因為你根本不懂。
No, come on.
才不會，拜託告訴我嘛。
You don't have any of these cute little obsessive things.
因為妳全身上下一點這可愛且瘋狂的固執點都沒有。
No, that's not true.
胡說，哪有這種事。
That is not true.
這絕對不是真的。
Oh, yeah?
真的嗎？
Yeah.
對啊。
All right, well, tell me one of yours.
太好了，拿你就跟我說一個你的。
Okay.
好喔。
Ah!
啊哈！
One of my things is
其中一個就是──
I always separate
我總是會將我的毛巾襪
my sweat socks from my dress socks.
和一般的襪子全部分開來。
Yeah.
對。
What if they get mixed up?
那如果搞混了呢？
Boy, I would just, uh...
天啊，我這人大概就會直接、呃...
I would freak out.
我真的會崩潰。
You would not.
你才不會崩潰。
Oh, I can't believe this.
天啊這真的教我沒法相信。
I hate this. You're too normal.
我討厭這樣。我看你真的很不正常喔。
I can't believe my boyfriend doesn't have a thing.
我簡直無法去相信我的男朋友竟然沒有問題！
My boyfriend doesn't have a thing.
我的男朋友竟然沒有問題！
See, if anyone overheard that,
你聽著，如果剛剛那些被任何人聽到，
I didn't come off well there.
他們對我不會有好評價的。
Hey.
嘿。
Mr. Douglas is looking for you.
道格拉斯先生在找你。
Why? Why?
為什麼？
Why is Mr. Douglas looking for me?
為何道格拉斯先生要找我？
Because he has a strong suspicion
因為他強烈懷疑
that you dropped the ball on the Lender Project.
你搞砸了放款專案的進度。
Why? Why?
為什麼？
Why does he suspect that?
為什麼他會懷疑是我？
Because at first, he thought it was Joseph.
因為起初，他以為那是約瑟夫搞的。
But after he asked Joseph about it,
但當他去問了約瑟夫後，
it turns out it was you.
原來那個人是你。
Anyway, I just thought you should know.
無論如何，我只是想你知道這回事。
All right, that's it.
好啦，就這樣。
Look, Joey, I'm sorry.
聽好，喬伊，我很抱歉。
I realize this is the role of a lifetime for you,
我知道這角色對你來說很重要，
and if I could just fire Joseph, I would.
如果能開除約瑟夫的話，我會馬上做。
But unfortunately, that's not possible,
但不幸的是，這已經是不可能的，
so I'm gonna have to let both of you go.
所以我必須得讓你們離開。
What are you talking about? Everybody loves Joseph.
你在胡說八道甚麼啊？大家都超愛約瑟夫的。
I don't. I hate Joseph.
我可沒有。我痛恨約瑟夫。
Okay?
你了解嗎？
I think he's a brown-nosing suck-up.
我認為他就是個厚顏無恥的馬屁精。
Oh, yeah?
噢？是嗎？
Well, you can't fire Joseph.
但我告訴你，你無法開除約瑟夫。
You know why? Because he's not in your department.
你知道為什麼嗎？因為他不歸你管。
Oh!
噢！
Yeah.
對啊。
All right, okay.
好吧。
All right, so I can't fire Joseph,
好，既然我沒辦法炒他魷魚，
but, uh, I can sleep with his wife.
但我能跟我老婆睡啊！
Karen?
凱倫？
Yeah, Karen.
沒錯，凱倫！
I'm thinking about having an affair with her.
我正想和她發生婚外情呢。
Oh, you know what?
噢，你猜怎麼著？
I just did.
我剛做了。
What the hell are you doing to me, man?
搞什麼鬼，你怎麼可以這樣老兄？
Oh, well, it's not me.
喔，這可不是我做的。
It's my character.
這是我的角色幹的。
Chandy.
錢弟。
Yeah, the rogue processor
沒錯，這流氓資料處理員
who seduces his co-workers' wives for sport
只是為了好玩而勾引他同事的老婆，
and then laughs about it the next day at the water cooler.
然後隔天早上，在辦公室的茶水間譏笑這件事。
In fact, I have her panties
而事實上，她的內衣
right there in my drawer.
就剛好放在我的抽屜裡而已！
Really?
真的？
No, freak show! She's fictional!
沒有這種東西啦，神經病！她可是虛構的老婆耶！
Hey, take it easy.
嘿，別那麼氣嘛。
If it means that much to you,
如果這對你來說有那麼重要，
I'll, uh, I'll go find something else.
我會...我會去找別的事情做。
Thank you.
感謝你。
It's just that
我只是覺得，
I'm gonna miss Joseph.
我會很想念約瑟夫。
I liked him.
我很喜歡這傢伙。
His wife. She was hot.
他太太真惹火。
And the kids.
而且他還有小孩。
You know, he was gonna put in a pool
你知道，他本來還要在院子裡弄一個游泳池，
next summer.
在下個夏天。
Ow!
噢！
Please take these off. I swear I won't scratch.
請幫我們把這些手套拖下來。我發誓我們絕對不會抓了。
Oh, sorry, hon.
噢很抱歉，甜心。
Monica's orders.
這是摩妮卡的命令。
Well, that wasn't easy.
喔，要綁這個還真的不簡單。
Okay, dinner's on.
好了，準備吃晚餐了。
And there's a peach cobbler
我還在烤箱裡放了水蜜桃派在加熱，
warming in the oven,
所以盤子會燙燙的喔，
so the plate's gonna be hot,
但對你們現在這樣來說，絕對不會是個問題。
but that shouldn't be a problem for you.
畢竟你們兩手都是手套嘛。
All right,
好了，
you kids, bye now.
小朋友們，再會囉。
Bye!
掰！
Oh, look, look, look, a low-budget puppet show.
噢！你看你看，這是場極低成本的木偶秀耶。
It's such a shame you can't see
要是你能看得到我對著你比出
what finger I'm holding up.
什麼手指的話該有多好啊。
Wine?
倒紅酒了嗎？
Please.
麻煩你。
Well,
喔，
spilled some.
撒了一點出來。
I got it.
我來擦。
I must tell you,
我必須和你說，
you look beautiful tonight.
今晚的你看起來真美麗。
What?
你說什麼？
Sorry.
抱歉。
You look beautiful.
你看起來很美麗。
Oh.
噢。
Okay, you know what? That's it.
好，你知道嗎？管它的。
That's it.
管它的了。
Oh.
噢。
Oh, yes.
噢，對。
Oh, good.
奧，好棒。
Oh.
噢。
Monica.
摩妮卡。
Wake up.
醒醒。
Monica.
摩妮卡。
What's up?
怎麼了？
I thought of a thing.
我想了個問題。
Yeah?
啊哈？
Yeah.
是啊。
I have to sleep,
我一定要睡，
have to, on this side of the bed.
只能睡這張床的這一側。
No, honey.
怎麼會呢，親愛的。
You have to sleep on this side of the bed
你會睡在這一側，
because I have to sleep on this side of the bed.
完全是因為我非得睡在另一側喔。
Or so I would have you believe.
我這人也是會講講這種鬼話讓你相信的。
No.
真的啦。
Big deal, so you have a side of the bed.
這又是什麼大不了的，不就是你只認定一邊側的床。
Everybody has a side of the bed.
每個人都會有這麼認床的時候。
Hey, come on.
聽著，別這樣。
You haven't heard my reason yet.
你還沒聽到我這麼說的理由。
All right, go on.
好啦，繼續說啊。
Okay.
好吧。
I have to sleep on the west side
非得睡在那一側
because I grew up
是因為我在加州
in California
長大，如果不這樣睡
and otherwise
不然的話
the ocean would be on the wrong side.
那我就面相了反方向的海洋了。
Oh, my God.
我的老天啊。
You're a freak.
你是個怪胎。
Yeah.
耶。
How about that?
覺得怎樣啊？
So, Ryan, where are you shipping off to?
那麼，瑞安你現在要去哪裡出發？
I really can't say.
這我這得沒法跟你說。
So do you have any, like, nuclear weapons on board?
你有什麼類似像是軍事武器嗎在船上的
I can't say.
這我不能說啊
Well, do you get to look through one of those, like,
那你應該有在那隻望過潛艇裡的
those periscope thingies?
望遠鏡的那些吧？
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
抱歉，但我真的沒法跟你講。
Well, it's neat learning about submarines.
嗯，學這些關於潛水艇的事還真令人愉悅。
I've got to get out of here.
總之我得離開了。
I'm going to miss my flight.
不然我會趕不上我的航班的。
Okay, I'll walk you out.
可以，陪你走下去。
Bye, Ryan. Pleasure. Nice to meet you.
掰瑞安我很榮幸。這真高興見到你
Take care.
慢走啊
So do you, uh, think we could get you
那你，我們可以在哪裡買到你身上
one of those, uh, uniform things?
那件軍用制服嗎？
You like that, do you?
怎麼你喜歡這件嗎？
Oh, yeah.
對呀。
I'll make some calls. Okay.
我幫你找找好嗎。好。
Can you believe this is how we spent
你能想像得到我們的兩個禮拜
our two weeks together?
就會是在這種情況下度過嗎？
I know. We didn't do any of the romantic things I had planned,
我很了解，我們甚至連任何一件我想浪漫跟你度過的事都還沒做，
like having a picnic in Central Park
比如說在中央公園裡野餐，
and, you know, a coffee at Central Perk.
還有，一起到中環咖啡廳買個卡拉。
Oh, I just got that.
喔天啊我也得了這該死的水痘。
Oh!
歐！
Taxi.
計程車！
Bye, you.
先走囉
Uh...
噁...
Oh, I'm sorry.
噢抱歉。
We're clo...
我們休...
Hey, sailor.
嘿水手。
Is this what you had in mind?
這是你想要的嗎？
I'll say.
我想絕對是。
Ooh!
喔！
I'm shipping out tomorrow.
明天得啟航了。
Well, then, uh...
既然這樣，
We better make this night count.
那今天這晚上可要有價值了。
Oh, wait! I forgot to shut off
啊！等等！我忘記去關
the cappuccino machine.
卡布起若的機器了。
Sorry.
抱歉。
Anchor's away.
拔錨了！
Oh, and my purse, my purse, my purse,
喔，然後我的包包、我的包包....
my purse, my purse, my purse.
包包阿。
Sorry.
抱歉喔。
Oh!
歐！
Oh, you know what? I forgot to turn off
你知道嗎？我忘了關
the bathroom light. Just...
浴室燈！你等我...
All right, you know, why don't I just meet you upstairs?
阿不管拉，不如我就在直接上面等妳吧？
Honey!
寶貝！